<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Real Estate Investing Made Easy</title>
    <description>If you are looking to buy or sell a home, get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from Ocean City Development - your professional  Real Estate Agents.</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2018 20:37:26 -0600</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2018 20:37:26 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.6.2</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Secret to Striking Great Deals as an Investor</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/VBI-c5gY7LY?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today, I’d like to share the most important thing there is to know when it comes to real estate investing, which is how to get a super low offer accepted.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I know what you’re thinking: The market is too hot right now, sellers want too much for their properties, and too many investors are competing over too few deals. Nevertheless, I’m going to tell you exactly how my team and I get over 100 investment deals accepted every single year, using super low offers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I remember the very first deal I got under contract with a super low offer. It was nearly 10 years ago, but I still vividly remember the feeling of disbelief I had after having that offer accepted. It wasn’t until I actually closed on that deal that it was ever going to happen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I made $115,000 on a wholesale deal thanks to a super low offer. It was a great feeling to get such an amazing deal. Actually, this deal is what launched my real estate investing career.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the end of the day, &lt;strong&gt;getting super low offers accepted doesn’t take the skills of a master negotiator.&lt;/strong&gt; My team doesn’t get great deals by being master negotiators; we get offers accepted based on statistics and having great volume.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Moving forward, something you must know is that 10% of the population is going to want to sell to an investor. No matter what you do when you’re face to face with a seller, only 10% of sellers will want to sell to an investor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So when you’re dealing with sellers, make sure they understand the benefits and drawbacks of selling to an investor. When my team and I go on a face-to-face appointment, we go over all of this. For those of you who don’t know, &lt;strong&gt;we buy in cash with no mortgage contingency, no formal inspection, and we close on the seller’s time frame.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the misconceptions about buying properties at a discount is that sellers will want to sell in seven, 10, or 14 days. Actually, the process can turn into somewhat of a waiting game. I’ve personally waited on a seller who had an 18-month time frame. But it was because of my team’s patience that we won the deal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Being willing to work with a seller’s time frame will be massively important to your success as an investor.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even so, it’s still true that only 10% of sellers will want to make a deal with an investor. With that being said, you’re probably wondering how my team and I manage to do 100 deals a year. The secret to how we get 100 deals a year is that we get in front of 1,000 sellers a year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=The secret to how we get 100 deals a year is that we get in front of 1,000 sellers a year.%20http://localhost:4000/2018/02/05/the-secret-to-striking-great-deals-as.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“The secret to how we get 100 deals a year is that we get in front of 1,000 sellers a year.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the end of the day, this is a lead generation game. In order to set up 1,000 face-to-face appointments per year, &lt;strong&gt;we have systems in place to help us book a minimum of 20 face-to-face appointments per week.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don’t push the seller to make a deal with you. Instead, do what is in their best interest. Give them all of the options and make sure they make the decision that’s right for them. 10% of the time, their best option will be to accept a discounted offer from you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And, because my team and I are partnering with investors across the country, the systems we use are available to you regardless of the market you’re in. We’re taking our lead generation systems and putting them in other geographic markets across the United States.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, &lt;strong&gt;if you want to get face to face with sellers and dominate your local market, go to&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.realestateinvestingiseasy.com&quot;&gt;www.realestateinvestingiseasy.com&lt;/a&gt;. Then, input your email to receive a video on the exact steps you’ll need to take in order to partner with me in your market.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even if you decide not to form a partnership with me, you’ll gain access to my private Facebook group “Questions for Tom.” Within that group, you can send me questions and receive an answer within just 24 hours.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When you enter your email, you’ll also get free tickets to my bi-monthly fix-and-flip events.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any other questions or would like more information, feel free to give me a call or send me an email. I look forward to hearing from you soon.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2018 15:47:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2018/02/05/the-secret-to-striking-great-deals-as.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2018/02/05/the-secret-to-striking-great-deals-as.html</guid>
        
        <category>Steps to Successful Real Estate Investment</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Phil Signs 6 Contracts This Month</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/612n52gByxA?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the call, Phil Castillo, who works with Tom in his Boston office, talks about his super-successful month where he got six properties under contract. Phil has been with Tom’s team for one year now and on the call we go back to his first days on the team (and specifically what some of his struggles were on day one), what the turning point was for him, and the advice that he would give to anyone going on face-to-face seller appointments today.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We also talk to Barbara, who is also on Tom’s team in Boston, and discuss an investment deal that she put under contract this week for $10,000 less than Tom’s original offer price.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Learn how to create an unlimited supply of face to face appointments at: www.getmotivatedsellerappointments.com.}&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2018 10:51:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/weeklyrecordings/2018/01/30/Phil-Signs-6-Contracts-This-Month.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/weeklyrecordings/2018/01/30/Phil-Signs-6-Contracts-This-Month.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>WeeklyRecordings</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>5 Real Estate Investing &quot;Don'ts&quot; to Avoid at All Costs</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/mUe9kJb-Nds?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today, I want to let you in on the things you shouldn’t be doing when it comes to marketing in real estate, as well as explain what you should do instead. These tips have been compiled over countless hours and millions of dollars spent on motivated seller marketing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Don’t market only when you need a deal.&lt;/strong&gt;  This is the biggest mistake I see newer real estate investors make. I call it the “real estate investing hangover.” New investors run around, market, find a great deal, then stop marketing. These investors spend all of their time on the fix and flip or on trying to wholesale the property. Then, all of a sudden, they wake up one day with no deals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is the real estate hangover I’m talking about. You get paid for the deal you just closed only to realize you don’t have any other deals in the works. In order to get face to face with motivated sellers, you must be constantly marketing. Don’t just market when you need a deal; you need to market all the time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. Don’t market to the same list as everyone else.&lt;/strong&gt; Lists of absentee owners, notices of default, and people behind on their mortgage are the same lists that everyone else will be pursuing. In fact, so many people market to these lists that your odds of getting a deal from them are very low. The name of the game in real estate investing is to have as little competition as possible on a home sale.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Instead of buying a motivated seller list, you should build a database of the homes in your market that you want to buy. To do this, you’ll first need to create a property avatar—a list of all characteristics of a home. In other words, make a list of the property characteristics that you like.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then, add the avatar of the particular seller. Ask yourself, what kind of sellers tend to sell to you? For me, the people who sell to me generally have equity and have lived in their home a long time. When you make a list of the kinds of properties you like and a list of the kinds of sellers who are likely to make a deal with you, and then combine those lists, you are setting yourself up for success.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=Don’t just market when you need a deal; you need to market all the time.%20http://localhost:4000/2018/01/26/5-real-estate-investing-donts-to-avoid.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“Don’t just market when you need a deal; you need to market all the time.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3. Don’t buy a super expensive website.&lt;/strong&gt; This is one thing I see newer investors doing all the time. As someone who has made this mistake myself, I can tell you that the thousands you’re spending aren’t worth it. You may end up with a gorgeous website, but this shouldn’t be the goal of your online presence. Your website needs to convert leads. Of course there’s nothing wrong with having a website that looks nice, but it isn’t entirely necessary. The main focus should be capturing contact information from people who visit it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Personally, I use Investor Carrot. Investor Carrot is a website company that creates sites specifically for real estate investors. Investor Carrot sites are designed to convert. Also, using Investor Carrot is actually less expensive than hiring a website developer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;4.  Don’t spend your marketing dollars on mass media campaigns.&lt;/strong&gt; When you advertise on television, radio, and billboards, you’re paying to reach people who have homes you don’t even want to buy. Instead of mass media advertising, focus your money and energy on targeted advertising. Utilize mailers, cold calling, and internet ads to generate leads.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;5. Don’t drive for dollars.&lt;/strong&gt; If you aren’t familiar with the concept, driving for dollars is when you drive through neighborhoods you’d like to buy in to find beat-up properties. Doing this is a huge waste of time. There is no correlation between a beat-up property and a seller who wants to sell at a discount. When you target beat-up homes, you’re cutting out your very best deals. In this market, your best deals are actually sellers who are willing to sell at a discount and whose properties are actually in decent shape.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Motivated sellers sell based on a specific life situation, not because their home isn’t in good shape. So, don’t drive for dollars. Instead, spend hours actually prospecting to the people in your database.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All of the mistakes I’ve shared today are things that have cost me money in the past. Aside from simply sharing this list, there is another way I’d like to help you make better investment choices. My team and I are partnering with investors in markets across the United States. We only make money when you make money. With that being said, &lt;strong&gt;if you would like to learn more about my marketing systems, visit &lt;a href=&quot;www.realestateinvestingiseasy.com&quot;&gt;www.realestateinvestingiseasy.com&lt;/a&gt; and enter your email.&lt;/strong&gt; After you’ve provided your email, you will be prompted to watch a webinar that will go over key marketing strategies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even if you aren’t interested in working with me, I still highly recommend visiting this website. Doing so will give you access to two major benefits. First, you’ll gain access to my private Facebook group called “Questions for Tom.” &lt;strong&gt;There, you can ask me questions anytime, and I will personally answer them within 24 hours.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The second benefit you gain from entering your email to this website is that you will get free tickets to all of my in-person training events.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any other questions or would like more information, feel free to give me a call or send me an email. I look forward to hearing from you soon.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2018 10:51:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2018/01/26/5-real-estate-investing-donts-to-avoid.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2018/01/26/5-real-estate-investing-donts-to-avoid.html</guid>
        
        <category>Steps to Successful Real Estate Investment</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Featured On the Best Ever Show: Fired Accountant Builds 150 Agent Brokerage </title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“I started as a CPA working at a CPA firm, but I knew from day one that job was a mistake. Because everyone kept pushing me, though, I kept plugging along. Every day I’d sit at my desk and read and daydream about real estate investing. It got to a point where I was having trouble completing my assignments at the firm, and they eventually fired me.”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;100%&quot; height=&quot;166&quot; scrolling=&quot;no&quot; frameborder=&quot;no&quot; src=&quot;https://w.soundcloud.com/player/?url=https%3A//api.soundcloud.com/tracks/385529510&amp;amp;color=ff5500&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now Tom is a full time investor and broker. He flips over 100 properties a year and buys all kinds of properties from single families up to 10 unit properties. Listen in to hear how Tom built his real estate business up from nothing, and how he’ll continue to grow.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2018 11:07:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2018/01/18/featured-on-best-ever-show-fired.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2018/01/18/featured-on-best-ever-show-fired.html</guid>
        
        <category>Interviews</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Using a Website in Your Real Estate Investment Business</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/Q30eMB24CVQ?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today we’re going to talk about how you can and should use a website in your real estate investing business. The reality is that getting a website on day one doesn’t make sense for a lot of people. I’m here to talk about what a website should be doing for you in your business when you’re ready for it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Here’s an outline of what I discussed, so you can skip ahead to the part in the video that interests you most:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;0:50- The only reason you need a website in the real estate business.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1:45- How to drive traffic to your website once you’re ready to have it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3:00- What not to do when building your website.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;5:35- An example of a website that successfully converts leads.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;6:45- What you should absolutely do when building your website.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;7:35- How I doubled my leads from my website by using Investor Carrot.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;8:30- How you can learn from my mistakes in developing your real estate investor business 
by becoming a true partner.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;9:30- How to find out that working with us in your market will look like.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re interested in becoming a partner, or you just have any questions about your website, lead conversion, or anything else, don’t hesitate to reach out to me at &lt;a href=&quot;www.realestateinvestingiseasy.com&quot;&gt;www.realestateinvestingiseasy.com&lt;/a&gt;. I’ll make sure you get free access to all of my in-person training events that are held each month. I look forward to hearing from you soon!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2018 10:26:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2018/01/18/using-website-in-your-real-estate.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2018/01/18/using-website-in-your-real-estate.html</guid>
        
        <category>Steps to Successful Real Estate Investment</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Secret to Striking Great Deals as an Investor</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/VBI-c5gY7LY?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today, I’d like to share the most important thing there is to know when it comes to real estate investing, which is how to get a super low offer accepted.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I know what you’re thinking: The market is too hot right now, sellers want too much for their properties, and too many investors are competing over too few deals. Nevertheless, I’m going to tell you exactly how my team and I get over 100 investment deals accepted every single year, using super low offers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I remember the very first deal I got under contract with a super low offer. It was nearly 10 years ago, but I still vividly remember the feeling of disbelief I had after having that offer accepted. It wasn’t until I actually closed on that deal that it was ever going to happen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I made $115,000 on a wholesale deal thanks to a super low offer. It was a great feeling to get such an amazing deal. Actually, this deal is what launched my real estate investing career.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the end of the day, &lt;strong&gt;getting super low offers accepted doesn’t take the skills of a master negotiator.&lt;/strong&gt; My team doesn’t get great deals by being master negotiators; we get offers accepted based on statistics and having great volume.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Moving forward, something you must know is that 10% of the population is going to want to sell to an investor. No matter what you do when you’re face to face with a seller, only 10% of sellers will want to sell to an investor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So when you’re dealing with sellers, make sure they understand the benefits and drawbacks of selling to an investor. When my team and I go on a face-to-face appointment, we go over all of this. For those of you who don’t know, &lt;strong&gt;we buy in cash with no mortgage contingency, no formal inspection, and we close on the seller’s time frame.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the misconceptions about buying properties at a discount is that sellers will want to sell in seven, 10, or 14 days. Actually, the process can turn into somewhat of a waiting game. I’ve personally waited on a seller who had an 18-month time frame. But it was because of my team’s patience that we won the deal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Being willing to work with a seller’s time frame will be massively important to your success as an investor.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even so, it’s still true that only 10% of sellers will want to make a deal with an investor. With that being said, you’re probably wondering how my team and I manage to do 100 deals a year. The secret to how we get 100 deals a year is that we get in front of 1,000 sellers a year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the end of the day, this is a lead generation game. In order to set up 1,000 face-to-face appointments per year, &lt;strong&gt;we have systems in place to help us book a minimum of 20 face-to-face appointments per week.&lt;/strong&gt; 
&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=The secret to how we get 100 deals a year is that we get in front of 1,000 sellers a year.%20http://localhost:4000/2018/01/18/the-secret-to-striking-great-deals-as.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“The secret to how we get 100 deals a year is that we get in front of 1,000 sellers a year.”&lt;/a&gt;
Don’t push the seller to make a deal with you. Instead, do what is in their best interest. Give them all of the options and make sure they make the decision that’s right for them. 10% of the time, their best option will be to accept a discounted offer from you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And, because my team and I are partnering with investors across the country, the systems we use are available to you regardless of the market you’re in. We’re taking our lead generation systems and putting them in other geographic markets across the United States.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, &lt;strong&gt;if you want to get face to face with sellers and dominate your local market, go to &lt;a href=&quot;www.realestateinvestingiseasy.com&quot;&gt;www.realestateinvestingiseasy.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt; Then, input your email to receive a video on the exact steps you’ll need to take in order to partner with me in your market.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even if you decide not to form a partnership with me, you’ll gain access to my private Facebook group “Questions for Tom.” Within that group, you can send me questions and receive an answer within just 24 hours.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When you enter your email, you’ll also get free tickets to my bi-monthly fix-and-flip events.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any other questions or would like more information, feel free to give me a call or send me an email. I look forward to hearing from you soon.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2018 10:06:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2018/01/18/the-secret-to-striking-great-deals-as.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2018/01/18/the-secret-to-striking-great-deals-as.html</guid>
        
        <category>Steps to Successful Real Estate Investment</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Worst Way to Invest in Real Estate</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/Q4o6KoFJUao?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Are you worried about losing money through real estate investing? If you’re using it the wrong way, then you should be. And the worst way to invest in real estate is by taking market exposure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Taking market exposure means whether or not you make money on the deal depends on what happens with the real estate market. Even though nobody can tell you exactly where the market is going, as of now, there is a lot more possibility for the market to go down than for it to continue to go up. If you’re fixing and flipping and investing in real estate, make sure you’re taking as little of that market exposure as possible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How do you avoid this mistake?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First, &lt;strong&gt;if you’re doing a fix and flip, make sure you’re doing a project with a very quick turn.&lt;/strong&gt; You don’t want to take on really long projects that could last a year or more. You want to take on projects that allow you to buy and sell in the exact same market. The great thing about the real estate market, as opposed to the stock market or the bond market, is that when it’s going down, it can’t happen all at once by the function of how real estate is sold.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The stock market can go down 20% or 30% over the course of a few months—sometimes even faster than that. When the real estate market goes down, it goes down slowly, and the real estate market goes down once inventory starts to accumulate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By “quick-turn” projects, I mean projects you can buy, renovate, or sell within a 90-day period in the same market. That eliminates the risk of market exposure instead of buying a property, renovating it, and selling it a year later. Even though the real estate market goes down slowly, a lot can change in one year. One year is a long enough period of time to lose 10% to 15% value on a project, which is why you want to fix and flip in 90 days or less. If the market falls 12% over the course of a year and you were able to fix and flip in 90 days, you’d only be taking on 3% of that 12% exposure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Another thing you can do to eliminate market exposure is to wholesale.&lt;/strong&gt; In our current market, there’s no better opportunity than wholesaling. Not only are homeowners overpaying for deals, but investors are overpaying for deals too. In some markets, people doing wholesale deals are making the same, and in some cases more, than the people they’re wholesaling the contracts to.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re unfamiliar with the concept of wholesaling, all it means is that when you get a property under contract, you give that contract to another investor for a fee. When you wholesale a deal, there’s no defined amount you can make, but typically speaking, people in this market are making anywhere from $10,000 to $30,000. What you make on a wholesale deal is dependent on what kind of deal you get. The better deal you get, the more you’ll make.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The third thing you can to do avoid market exposure is if you’re buying a multi-family property, make sure the cash flows on day one. Never buy a rental property based on appreciation—it should be cash-flow positive from day one. There are some markets across the country where this is almost an impossibility. Even in our market here in Boston, it’s tough to buy properties where the cash flows from day one, but you can’t let that rule stop you. Make sure you’re getting great deals and properties below market value so they produce cash flow from day one.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To summarize, doing lengthy projects in our market is very dangerous. If you’re going to close on a property, make sure it’s a quick-turn project. If you don’t want any market exposure whatsoever, wholesale the property. If you’re buying a property to buy and hold, make sure it’s cash-flow positive from day one.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=Never buy a rental property based on appreciation.%20http://localhost:4000/2018/01/09/the-worst-way-to-invest-in-real-estate.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“Never buy a rental property based on appreciation.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another thing you can do to make sure you don’t repeat mistakes others have made is by working with me directly in your market. I’m looking to expand into other geographic markets across the US to implement my systems and tools. This can benefit you because it will prevent you from making the same rookie mistakes that I made.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re interested in what a true partnership looks like, visit &lt;a href=&quot;www.realestateinvestingiseasy.com&quot;&gt;www.realestateinvestingiseasy.com&lt;/a&gt; and enter your email address. Once you do that, you’ll get a copy of the video I’ve created that will go into further detail of what working with me in your market will look like in a true partnership fashion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even if you don’t want to work with me, you can still benefit from entering your email address on my website. It will grant you lifetime free access to any of my fix-and-flip events I host every other month. You’ll also get free access to my private Facebook group “Questions for Tom” where you can ask me any real estate question you want and I will answer it within 24 hours.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any other questions, don’t hesitate to reach out to me. I’d be happy to help you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2018 13:03:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2018/01/09/the-worst-way-to-invest-in-real-estate.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2018/01/09/the-worst-way-to-invest-in-real-estate.html</guid>
        
        <category>Steps to Successful Real Estate Investment</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Phil Signs 6 Contracts This Month</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/eyRepld27XQ?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’ve never done an investment deal before, it can sometimes be hard to believe that anyone would WANT to take less than market value for their home.  On the later part of the call, we discuss all of the major reasons why sellers sell to us at a discount.  In the beginning part of the call, we discuss how to get all family members on the same page in order to get a contract signed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then, we will open the floor to the rest of the group. You will be able to give us the play by play of what happened on your face to face appointment, and then we will give you feedback on different techniques to use in order to turn the appointment into cold, hard, cash.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have gone on a seller appointment this week, please come prepared to talk about it. The more feedback that you are able to get on your face to face appointments, the more money you will put in your pocket.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Learn how to create an unlimited supply of face to face appointments at: &lt;a href=&quot;www.getmotivatedsellerappointments.com&quot;&gt;www.getmotivatedsellerappointments.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2018 10:51:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/weeklyrecordings/2018/01/09/Why-Do-Sellers-Sell-To-Investors-Anyway.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/weeklyrecordings/2018/01/09/Why-Do-Sellers-Sell-To-Investors-Anyway.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>WeeklyRecordings</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How We Turned Our Latest Fix-and-Flip into a $50,000 to $70,000 Profit</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/XcGzSpYgyJ8?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Welcome to one of our latest fix-and-flip properties at 21 Center Avenue in Reading, Massachusetts!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This property was purchased three months ago for $305,000. We put in $60,000 worth of repairs, and we just recently got the project under contract for $500,000. All told, we’re probably looking at a $50,000 to $70,000 net profit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Follow along in the video above to get a full tour of this property and hear me explain some of the fix-and-flip processes we used to turn this house into a profit. &lt;strong&gt;For your convenience, I’ve included timestamps below so you can skip ahead to certain sections that might interest you:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(1:17) - A split-level entry that allows you to walk upstairs to the first floor or downstairs to the second floor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(2:08) - Our fully staged living room, dining room, and kitchen layout on the first floor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(5:04) - The upper-level bathroom.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(5:55) - Upper-level bedroom No. 1.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(6:21) - Upper-level bedroom No. 2, featuring new windows.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(6:52) - Upper-level bedroom No. 3.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(7:17) - Lower-level bedroom No. 1&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(9:52) - The lower-level den, featuring a fireplace.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(10:15) - The lower-level bathroom, which we made into a full bathroom.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(10:45) - Key points to remember about fixing and flipping.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If you want to learn more tips and tricks to flipping properties or you’d like to work with me directly on fix-and-flip properties, visit &lt;a href=&quot;www.realestateinvestingiseasy.com&quot;&gt;www.realestateinvestingiseasy.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt; By entering your email address on that website, you’ll get free access to any of my fix-and-flip training events and free access to my private Facebook group “Questions for Tom,” where I’ll answer any of your real estate investment questions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks so much for walking through this property with me. If you have any other questions, feel free to give me a call or send me an email. I’ look forward to hearing from you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2018 16:45:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2018/01/02/how-we-turned-our-latest-fix-and-flip.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2018/01/02/how-we-turned-our-latest-fix-and-flip.html</guid>
        
        <category>Motivational</category>
        
        <category>Opportunity</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Surprising Revelation...</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/JpFv8LPnS00?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last week we were honored to have Jody Gann out of Birmingham Alabama fly out to our office.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While here, we did a behind the scenes look at our real estate business that fixes and flips over 100 houses per year, has allowed us to accumulate over 300 rental properties and net over 7 figures by having a 200 person real estate brokerage team that brings us deals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Watch the video above and see Jody get coached on his 90 play and the surprising revelation he had when coming out to visit.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2018 14:26:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2018/01/02/surprising-revelation.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2018/01/02/surprising-revelation.html</guid>
        
        <category>Opportunity</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
